從前
Once upon a time.
很久以前
A very long time ago,
第一波吸血鬼出現的時候
back when the first vamp showed up,
有一個男人
there was a man.
先生
Mister!
是的 先生
-Yeah, Mister.
先生是有史以來最強的獵人
Well, Mister was the best hunter that there ever was.
他途經刑柱之地 消滅吸血鬼
And he traveled the Stakelands killing vamps.
然後有一天 他碰到了一個男孩
And then one day he came upon this boy.
當時那個男孩處境非常危險
He was in real trouble.
一隻龐大的壞蛋吸血鬼
You see, there was this big bad vamp
就要把他給吃了
that was gonna eat him up!
不要
No.
是啊
Yeah.
但是先生出現了
But Mister showed up
他用尖木棍直插 吸血鬼的心臟
and he staked that vamp right through his heart.
耶
Yay!
在那之後
And after that,
他們來到北方他們遇到了一個女孩
they came up north and they met a girl.
是媽咪
' Mommy!
是的 是你媽咪
Yeah, it was mommy.
那個男孩和女孩相愛了
And the boy and this girl they fell in love.
然後你就出現了
And then you came along.
先生後來怎麼樣了
What happened to Mister?
我不知道寶貝
I don't know, baby.
有一天 我醒來後 他已經離開了
One day I woke up and he was gone.
我發現這條項鏈掛在一輛車的側邊
I found this necklace hanging on the side of a car.
他留下它 這樣我總是能記起他
He left it so that I would always remember him.
他們都死了
They're dead.
你還活著
You're alive.
像個活著的樣兒
Act like it.
我馬上回來 寶貝
I'll be right back, baby.
要我跟你一起去嗎
Do you want me to go with you?
不這次不行
No, not this time.
你要留在她身邊
I want you to stay with her.
好吧
Okay.
好的
Okay,
再見
bye.
他們帶了狂暴者來
They got berserkers!
他們會殺死我們所有人的
They're gonna kill us all!
除了我
Not me.
所以你跟在我身邊明白嗎
So you stay close, you understand?
我想留在這兒
I wanna stay.
安靜寶貝 保持安靜
Hush, baby, you just stay quiet.
馬丁
Martin?
放下吧 男孩
Put it away, boy.
我們無法改變過去
We don't do history.
譯名: 刑柱之地2/末日血慌(台)
這個世界不是在一聲巨響中死去的
The world didn't die with a bang.
它是在一聲尖叫中死去
It died with a scream.
大量的尖叫聲
Lots of them.
我都聽到了
And I heard 'em all.
什麼也沒剩下
There's nothing left,
一片垂死的景象
but a dying landscape.
很久前 人們就已經停止了重建
People stopped trying to rebuild a long time ago.
我們任其土崩瓦解
We let it all fall apart.
現在到處一片死寂
And now everything's quiet.
空蕩
Empty-
你在數周內都可能遇不到一個活人
You can go for weeks without finding a soul.
日夜更替
The days come and night falls.
我們要麼活下來 要麼死去
And we survive or we die.
我們所擁有的只剩回憶
All you really got are your memories
還有明天 前提是你夠幸運
and tomorrow, if you're lucky.
新伊甸是我僅存的家園
New Eden was the only home I had left.
而她
And she...
她從我手裏奪走了它
she took it from me.
兄弟會稱她為"母親"
The Brotherhood called her "The Mother".
那些吸血鬼崇拜者們
Those vamp worshipers
終於找到了他們的彌賽亞
finally found their Messiah.
那個被派來掃清世界上罪惡的人
The one sent to wipe the earth clean of sin.
（我們都是她的孩子↑）
我向南進入刑柱之地
I was heading south into the Stakelands.
如果他還活著
If he was still alive,
那就是我能找到他的地方
that's where I'd find him...
先生
Mister,
那個最接近家人的人
closest thing to family I had.
人們都知道他
People knew of him.
還有他單槍匹馬和
Of his one-man war against the Brotherhood
兄弟會吸血鬼們戰鬥的故
and the vamps.
他是個傳奇
He was a legend.
他是最後一個獵人
He was the last hunter.
如果我想找到那個女吸血鬼
If I wanted to get to her,
我就需要他的幫助
I was gonna need his help.
美國邊界線 10公里
放下 箭孩子
Drop it, son.
他們出來的時間早了點
They've been coming out earlier.
冒著見光的風險
Chancing the light...
鋌而走險
getting desperate.
你從哪裏來的
Where are you coming from?
北方 新伊甸來的
Up north. New Eden.
那你現在離家很遠了
You're a long way from home.
你在這裏做什麼
What are you doing here?
我在找人
I'm looking for someone.
都叫他先生
He's called Mister.
是的 聽說過他
Yeah, heard of him...
還以為他死了
thought he was dead.
這個可憐的男孩看起來餓了
The poor boy looks hungry.
敢不老實的話 孩子
You try anything, son,
我會把你切成兩半
I'll cut you in half.
噢 別說了 卡爾
Oh, shush, Karl,
你看不出他是個好男孩嗎
can't you see he's a nice boy?
來吧
Come on.
她不讓你吃飽了是不會罷休的
She won't be satisfied 'till you're fed.
天很快就黑了
Be dark soon anyway.
最好到裏面去
Best get inside.
味道很好 夫人 謝謝您
It's good, ma'am, thank you.
抱歉沒有肉吃
Sorry there's no meat.
現有條件下 我們只能這樣勉強應付了
We gotta make do with what we have.
你們不吃嗎
You uh... you're not eating?
我們吃過了
We ate already.
我們的兒子沃爾特去了加拿大
Our boy Walter went to Canada,
在那裏已經有孩子了
had a child up there,
他從沒回來過
never came back.
也許你知道他
Maybe you know of him?
沃爾特·阿姆斯特朗
Walter Armstrong?
別這樣 吉恩
Come on, Jean.
都多少年了
It's been years.
沃爾特就算沒死也差不多了
Walter is dead or as good as.
放棄了希望
Give up hope,
就和坐著等死沒什麼兩樣
you might as well lay down and die.
這個男孩在滿目瘡痍的世界中走失了
The boy is lost and alone in a world
孤獨無依
of woe.
但是他正在尋找自己的目標
And yet here he is looking for something.
這就是希望
That's hope.
在這種時刻
Times like these...
希望是我們繼續前進的唯一動力
it's all we got to keep us going.
去把沃爾特的床鋪好 卡爾
Make up Walter's bed for him, Karl.
謝謝你 夫人
Thank you, ma'am.
壞事發生在好人身上
Bad things happen to good people.
這世界並不公平
World ain't fair.
永遠也不會公平
Never will be.
但仍有好的東西可以去尋找
There's good to be found.
157人死於襲擊
南部松樹林的襲擊事件
不時有人穿過這裏
People pass through now and again.
我從他們那裏打聽新聞
I get what news they have,
更新我的地圖 寫下他們的故事
update my maps, write down their stories.
什麼
Why?
愛好而已
Just a hobby.
誰知道呢 如果這場災難有結束的一天
Who knows, this thing ever ends
也許人們會想知道曾經發生過什麼
people might wanna know what happened.
我們活在一個奇怪的時代
Yeah, it's strange times we're living in.
這是新黑暗時代 現在就是這樣
It's the new dark ages, that's what this is.
你沒事吧 孩子
You okay, son?
沒事我只是
Yeah, I just got a...
你應該坐下
You should sit down.
是的 奇怪的時代
Yep, strange times.
你看起來很累
You seem pretty tired.
你最好就在這兒睡下
Probably best you sleep right here.
噢不 吉恩 親愛的
Oh no, Jean! Honey!
哦 親愛的
Oh, honey.
對不
I'm sorr--
兄弟們 姐妹們
Brothers and sisters,
我們的族母已經復活了
...The mother of our blood has risen.
虔誠者將得到護佑
The devout will be saved.
異端者會被處死
The heretics will die.
加入我們 加入我們
Join us. Join us.
兄弟姐妹們
Brothers and sisters,
我們按照她的願景建造這個世界
we know the world in Her image.
你們不必再生病 飢餓 勞累
You need not be sick, hungry, tired.
弟會將給你衣物 食物
The Brotherhood will clothe you, feed you,
住所
shelter you.
母親的愛無邊無界
The Mother's love knows no bounds.
加入我們
Join us.
兄弟會只為她效力
The Brotherhood serves Her and Her alone.
兄弟們 姐妹們
Brothers and sisters,
我們的族母已經復活了
the mother of our blood has risen.
虔誠者將得到護佑
The devout will be saved.
異端者會被處死
The heretics will die.
加入我們 加入我們
Join us. Join us.
兄弟姐妹們
Brothers and sisters,
我們按照她的願景建造這個世界
rebuild a world in Her image.
你們不必再生病 飢餓 勞累
You need not be sick, hungry, tired--
嘿
Hey there.
媽的 哥們 你嚇了我一跳
Shit, man, you scared me.
你從哪裏來的
Where are you coming from?
加拿大
Canada.
鳴額
Hmm.
這裏怎麼樣
How's things here?
靜悄悄
Quiet.
你要交易什麼
What you got for trade?
不交易 我只是來找人的
You keep that, I'm just looking for somebody.
這裏除了我沒別人
Well, nobody here but me.
你在找那個獵人
You you looking for the hunter.
你 還有兄弟會那幫人也在找
You and them Brotherhood boys,
哦 他們可不太喜歡他
they don't like him much.
不 先生
No, sir.
你呢 你看見他了嗎
What about you? You seen him?
是的 是的
Yeah, yeah, I...
是我見過他
Yeah, I seen him.
在哪裏
When?
幾個月前
Few months back.
他往哪裏去了
Where was he headed?
封鎖區
Lockdown.
往西走了
West...
朝唐納希維爾去了
towards Donnersville.
唐納希維爾 在哪裏 我怎麼去那兒
Donnersville, where is that? How do I get there?
最快得走71號公路
Quickest way up is 71.
經過那個老磚廠
Past the old brick plant.
沒問題的
Good folk.
那裏是這附近唯一安全的地方
That's the only safe place around these parts.
好的 明白 非常感謝您的幫助
Alright, well, thank you very much for your help.
後會有期 加拿大
See you around, Canada.
嗨
Hi.
別害怕 寶貝 我不會傷害你
Don't worry, sweetheart, I'm not gonna hurt you.
我叫馬丁 你叫什麼名字
I'm Martin. What's your name?
世界上大部分的善都消失了
Most of the good in the world is gone.
仇恨
Hate...
仇恨似乎是唯一在生長的東西
hate seems to be the only thing that grows anymore.
想成為惡魔並不需要尖牙
You don't need fangs to be a monster.
他們比吸血鬼更壞
They're worse than the vamps.
是他們自己選擇了這樣
They chose this.
女士們 先生們
Ladies and Gentlemen,
盡情欣賞那隻野獸吧
feast your eyes on the Behemoth!
但首先 咱們先來個廝殺開胃菜
But first, an appetizer of mayhem.
一場沒有規則的死亡之戰
A mano a mano, no-rules death match!
現在 有請狂暴者的剋星
And now, The Bane of Berserkers,
暴力總督
The Viceroy of Violence,
無法擊敗的刑柱之主
The undefeated... The Stakelander!
先生
Mister?!
Mister.
先生 是我
Mister, it's me.
是我啊 白癡
Mister, it's me, you fucking idiot!
馬丁
Martin?
是
Yes.
不打就得死
Fight or die!
我們走吧
Let's go!
怎麼了
What?
退後
Back up.
這是個防範措施
It's a precaution.
是兄弟會幹的嗎
Was it Brotherhood?
是一個女吸血鬼幹的
It was the she-vamp.
她和兄弟會合作
She was working with The Brotherhood.
他們伏擊了我們
They ambushed us.
不知從哪兒突然冒出來的
Came out of nowhere.
她和其它的吸血鬼一起
She had other vamps with her...
還有那些狂暴者
Berserkers.
他們的組織
And they were organized,
像一支軍隊
like an army.
她似乎能控制它們
Like she had some kind of control over them.
我從來沒有見過那樣的事
I've never seen anything like it.
我試圖救她們 但
I tried to save them but...
我們能殺她嗎
Can we kill her?
你一生都在面對死亡 孩子
You got your whole life to die, kid,
沒必要趕著去送死
no point in rushing it.
放手吧
Let it go.
我不能
I can't.
男人把生命都用在報仇上
A man who spends his life on revenge...
他可能同時也給自己挖了兩個墳墓
He might as well dig two graves.
我確實這樣
I did.
我們給女兒起名貝爾
We named our daughter Belle.
你還記得貝爾嗎
Do you remember Belle?
每個人我都記得 孩子
I remember everybody, kid.
他們大多死了
And most of them are dead.
嘿
HEY-
我想一小時後上那條路
I wanna be on the road in about an hour.
我不知道你急什麼 孩子
I don't know what the hurry is, kid.
她怎麼了
What is with her?
她是個野孩子
She's feral,
可能是在野外自己長大的
probably raised herself up in the wilds.
我以前見過這樣的
I seen it before.
嘿
Hey.
過來 過來 沒事的
Come here, come here, it's okay.
就是這樣現在
That's it now.
可以了
There you go.
這是音樂 好聽
It's music. It's good.
就是這樣
That's it, yeah.
馬丁 移桌子
Martin, move the table!
進去嗎
In there?!
是的
Yeah.
還有武器
Your weapons!
不 進洞去
No, in the hole!
女孩 快快過來
Girl, come on, come on. Move!
下去 下去
Attagirl, down in there! Down in there.
馬丁 給
Martin, here!
不 不 等等
No, no, wait!
等等 你在幹什麼
Wait, what are you doing?
他在這裏
He's in here! Get that mother fucker!
兄弟們 姐妹們
Brothers and sisters,
該死的
Goddamn it!
不 不 不
No, no. No,no,no.
別擔心先生沒那麼容易死
Don't worry. Mister ain't easy to kill
而且他們沒看到我們
and they haven't see us.
我們會救他回來的
We'll get him back.
走吧
Come on.
噢 糟糕
Oh shit.
你媽個
You motherfucker.
我討厭吸血鬼
I hate vampires.
還有其它的嗎
Are there any more?
但願沒有
I hope not.
射得好 孩子
Nice shot, kid.
她把一個尖爪插進我肚子裏了
Ah, she put a claw in me.
我們得把它取出來
Alright, we've got to get it out.
不
No, leave it.
它插出了一個洞
It's pluggin' the hole.
是的 但你這樣會流血身亡的
Yeah, but you're gonna bleed to death.
你得幫我燒灼它
You're gonna have to cauterize it.
這兒的北邊有個封鎖區
There's a lockdown north of here.
那兒有一個醫生
They got a doc there...
別哭了
Oh, stop your crying,
我還沒死 女人
I ain't dead yet, woman.
我準備好了 孩子
I'm ready, kid.
使勁貼上去
Slap iron to it.
去找到他
Find him!
把那個婊子養的異族人帶回來
Bring that heathen son of a bitch back.
是頭兒
Yes, sir.
頭兒
Sir!
對不起 母親
I'm sorry, Mother,
他逃跑了
he escaped.
不知道是怎麼回事
I don't know how.
他
He...
有人幫他
he had help.
也不會跑遠的
He won't get far.
我 我已經派人去追他了
I've sent men after him...
請接受我最卑微的道歉族母
My humblest apologies, Mother of Our Blood.
請原諒我
Please forgive me.
你別管我了 孩子
Go on and leave me here, kid.
我會拖累你的
I'm slowing you down.
夠了 閉嘴
Alright, shut up.
我要保護你 爸爸 我哪也不去
I got your back, pappy. I ain't going nowhere.
你爸已經死了
I got your pappy swingin'.
我剛在後面不遠處看到一棵柳樹
I saw a willow tree a little ways back.
我去砍些樹皮來
I'll try to cut some bark.
那也許會幫你減輕痛苦
Maybe it'll help with your pain. Okay?
嘿 女孩
Hey, girl.
我叫先生
I'm Mister,
先生
Mister.
你的名字是女士
Your name is Lady.
先生
Mister...
女士
Lady.
你明白嗎
You understand?
這豈不是大走運了
Well, now, isn't this sweet?
敢動一下你就死定了 獵人
You move and you die, Hunter.
你給自己找了個小老婆
I see you got yourself a squaw doggie.
他對你來說有點老了 不是嗎
She's a little old for you, no?
嗚 我還從來沒抓到過小野人
Whoo! I never had a feral brat before!
我賭她會咬人
I bet you she bites.
你個小婊子
You little bitch!
現在你得付出代價
Oh, now you're gonna pay.
把槍放下
Drop it!
我讓你把槍放下 不然讓你見上帝去
I said, drop it or meet Jesus.
請 不要
No, please
馬丁
Martin!
別
No!
他還只是個孩子
He's just a boy.
你過來
You! Come here.
停下
That's enough.
你後面還有多少人
How many behind you?
只有我們幾個
It's just us.
我 還有你殺了的這些
Me and the men you killed.
我不是和他們一夥兒的
I'm not one of them,
我沒想做這些壞事
I don't wanna do any of this.
我 我真的不是
I'm really not...
可你穿著長袍
You're wearing the fucking robe.
他們逼我穿的
They made me.
他們威脅要把我喂吸血鬼
They said they'd feed me to the vamps.
我發誓
I swear.
要我做什麼都可以 求求你
I'll do anything. Please...
我真的不想死
I just don't wanna die.
你最好沒在撒謊 孩子
You better not be lying, boy,
我今天殺氣正盛
because I'm in a dick shooting mood today.
知道了 先生
Yes, sir.
放在十年前你已經殺了他
Ten years ago you would've shot him already.
我不喜歡這樣
I don't like it.
你不必喜歡
You don't have to like it.
在那邊加把勁
Over there, come on.
我想讓他再靠近些
I want him closer.
好的 放這裏 這兒
OK, here. Here, here.
你 跪地上
You, on the ground.
嘿 嘿 看著他
Hey, hey, on him.
喔 喔 嘿
Whoa, whoa, hey.
你真要這麼做嗎 孩子
You sure about that, boy?
這取決於你怎麼做
That's up to you.
你們在哪找到一個聖滾者的
*五旬節教派基督教徒 常有受聖靈感召而滿地打滾 或說話時舌頭失控
Where did you find the Holy Roller?
我們殺了其中兩個
We killed two of them,
他投降了
he surrendered.
他為什麼還活著
Why is he still alive?
因為他不讓我殺了他
Because he wouldn't let me kill him.
他怎麼了
What's With him?
他肚子上插著一個吸血鬼的爪
Got a vamp in his lung,
現在你們要射我們還是幫我們
now are you gonna shoot us or are you gonna help us?
他叫什麼
What's his name?
大家都叫他 先生
They call him Mister.
我是巴特
It's Bat.
你個婊子養的
You son of a bitch,
我以為你死了
I thought you were dead.
看起來像死了嗎
I look dead to you?
是 你看起來有點像死了
Yeah, you look a little dead.
你最近怎麼樣 老頭
How you doing, old timer?
再叫我老頭
You call me old timer again,
我會給你長長見識
you gonna find out.
哦 我知道
Oh, I know.
我很高興見到你
I'm so glad to see you.
別擔心 我們會治好你的
Don't worry, we'll get you fixed up.
現在殘餘的封鎖區不多
There aren't a lot of lockdowns left
而附近的那些個
and the ones that are still around
也不是你想要去的地方
ain't places you wanna be.
外面仍然有好的東西存在
There's still good out there.
我相信這點
I believe that.
但你遇到它的時候總是太晚
But it always finds you too late.
他們有防護牆 武器
They had walls, weapons...
我本應該滿懷希望的
I should have been hopeful.
長久以來第一次
That was the first time in a long time
我感覺到有安全感
that somewhere felt safe,
但我不能休息
but I couldn't rest.
因為她仍然還活著
Not while she was still out there.
我們給你帶了點吃的
I brought you something to eat.
吃完後 盤子放到外面來
Just push it back out when you're done.
哦 謝謝
Thank you.
等等 你叫什麼名字
Wait, what's your name?
比利
Billie.
It's Billie?
用我叔叔的名字給我起的
They named me after my uncle.
挺好的 我喜歡
It's nice, I like it.
我叫尤達
I'm Juda.
我得走了
I gotta go,
很高興見到你
It was nice to meet you.
拜拜
Bye.
放鬆點 女孩
Easy, girl.
他現在需要休息
He needs the rest now.
嘿 我叫厄爾
Hey, I'm Earl.
他怎麼樣了
How is he?
他是
He's...
嗯 他傷勢仍然比較嚴重
Well, he's mostly mean and ugly,
但我想他會挺過來的
but I think he'll make it.
他應該在幾天內能夠站起來
He should be up on his feet in a couple of days.
你是醫生嗎
So, you're a doctor?
是的 我是
Yeah, that I am.
嗯 我之前是一個獸醫
Well, I was a veterinarian,
但自從秋天以來 我基本在醫人
but since the fall I fix people up mostly.
肉 血 骨 道理都差不多
Flesh, blood, bone... it's all the same shit.
先生說你以前給他療過傷
Mister said that you'd that you'd patched him up before?
沒錯
That I did.
巴特和我們以前在墨西哥待過
Bat and I were with him in Mexico,
災難剛開始的時候
back in the beginning.
來 跟我來 我帶你看看房間
Come on. Come with me, I'll show you to your room.
女士 女士 走
Lady, Lady, come on.
走 走
Come on, come on.
尤達
Juda?
他們不會讓我出去
They ain't gonna let me out...
他們會
They're gonna...
他們會殺了我嗎
they're gonna kill me!
嘿 別這樣
Hey, come on.
嘿
Hey.
嗨
Hi.
你不會有事的
You're gonna be okay,
過些時間他們的態度就會軟化的
just gotta give them some time to soften up.
你不能 你不能放我出去嗎
Can't you... cant you just let me out?
我意思是 我不會惹事的
I mean, I don't want any trouble.
我只想逃走 求求你
I'll just run off. Please!
我不能
I can't.
求求你 比利 別走
Please, Billie, don't go.
這是一個老修道院
It's an old convent.
兄弟會把它從修女手裏奪走
The Brotherhood took it from the nuns
我們把它從兄弟會手裏奪過來
and we took it from the Brotherhood.
那是很久以前的事了
That was a ways back
那時還沒有組織得這麼井井有條
before they got so fucking organized.
每個人都各盡所能
Everybody pulls their weight here.
我們有老師
You got teachers,
我們有幾個木匠
we got a couple of carpenters,
我們還有退伍軍人
we got ex-military men...
他們都是好人
they're all good people.
四周有帶刺鐵絲網環繞
There's a barbed-wire fence that runs the perimeter,
這地方雖然看起來不咋地 但是通電
doesn't look like much but it's electrified
所以生活也更有趣
so that makes it fun.
是啊 我們在新伊甸有一些太陽能電池
Yeah, we had a couple of solar cells in New Eden but
但從來沒有產出這麼大的電力
never could have drawn this much power.
是我的兩個雙胞胎妹子在提供這些
Yeah, I got my twin girls for that.
看到那兩台發電機了嗎
See these two gennies?
他們為這整個地方提供電力
They power the whole damn fandango.
但你從來沒見過我最喜歡的部分
But you ain't even seen my favorite part.
可以淋浴了
The shower's free.
好的 女士 輪到你了
Alright, Lady, it's your turn.
走
Come on.
Come on!
到那兒去
Here you go.
給你準備了些乾淨的衣服
There's some clean clothes there for you.
到了 進去
There you go,
進去 女士
go ahead. Go ahead, Lady.
好 好 慢點 他媽的
Alright, alright! Take it easy, goddamn it.
你怎麼樣 老夥計
How are you feeling, old buddy?
噢 感覺就像一桶狗屎
Oh, like a bucket of shit.
我想喝一杯 你帶了嗎
I could use a drink. You carrying?
有點早了吧 不是嗎
It's a little early, ain't it?
這不在中國
Not in China.
對 你太瞭解我了
Yep, you know me too well.
給
Here you go.
墨西哥酒
Mexico.
墨西哥
我要在這裏躺多久
How long do I have to lay here?
噢 大約一兩天
Oh, I'd say just about a day or two.
把它給我
Gimme that.
為什麼
What?
這只能藥用
This is for medicinal purposes only.
給孩子嘗嘗拿著
Here, kid, you try it.
給 嘗嘗
Go ahead.
巴特自己釀的
Bat makes this stuff himself.
讓你雙蛋充滿活力
Make your balls bounce.
哦 是的 下流的東西
Oh yeah, that stuff is nasty.
下流 骯髒
Nasty, nasty.
讓他休息一下
Let's let the man rest a bit.
對
Yeah.
很高興再次見到你
Real good to see you again.
很高興見到你巴特
Good to see you, Bat.
你也走小女孩
Come on, you too, little girl.
別管她
Nah, leave her.
謝謝你醫生
Thanks, Doc.
好的
Yeah.
傷口痛的時候你就叫我來
Let me know if you need anything for the pain.
好的
Yeah.
尤達
Juda?
你還好嗎
You feelin' alright?
尤達
Juda?
哦 上帝啊 尤達
Oh my God! Juda!
當墨西哥被吸血鬼佔領後
When, uh, Mexico went vamp shit,
我們撤出了我們朝北走
we pulled out, we headed north.
先生在邊境區
Mister had a wife
娶了個老婆 生了個孩子
and a child across the border.
當時南方情況不好
It wasn't pretty down south.
很糟
It was bad.
簡直糟透了
Bad as it gets.
糟糕到他內心難以忍受
So bad that something snapped inside that man.
這就像一個
It was like a...
像一個開關
like a switch.
他當時腦子裏想的全是殺
All he wanted to do was kill.
他從來沒有抓到殺了他全家的那個
Well, he never got the one that killed his family,
所以我想 如果他殺不了那一個
so the way I figured it, if he couldn't get the one,
那他就會殺光它們所有
he'd get 'em all.
是啊 我們一起待了不久
But we stayed together for a while.
然後就分開了
And then we split.
他想到馬裏蘭去找他的夥伴
He wanted to check on his folks up in Maryland
巴特和我朝北走
and Bat and I we headed north.
是的
That's right.
和其它逃跑的人一起走
With everybody else who was running away.
是的 然後美國開始出現吸血鬼疫情
Yeah and then the shit hit the fan in the States.
一切美好的事物都破碎了
Whole fuckin' enchilada fell apart.
關於這一點
And on that note...
再喝一杯怎麼樣嗎
How about we get another drink?
哥們我十點鐘得去巡視指揮
And I got ten o'clock watch. I gotta head out.
你替我和他喝兩杯吧 小伙子
Now, you knock back a couple for me, young buck.
好的
Yeah.
嗨
Hi.
謝謝
Thanks.
咱們走 親愛的 走吧
Come on, honey. Come on.
小子
Boy!
婊子養的
Son of a bitch!
赫利俄準備好了嗎
*古希臘神話中的太陽神
ls Helios ready?!
差不多
Almost.
赫利俄斯是誰
Who's Helios?
夜晚的陽光寶貝兒
Sunshine in the nighttime, baby.
他們要衝破大門了
They're gonna ram the fucking gate!
快點 快
Coming up quick. Coming up quick.
來個人掩護我
Somebody cover me.
赫利俄斯開始
Helios now!
這就是送給你們這些混蛋的太陽神
That's Helios for your ass!
離窗戶遠點
Get away from the goddamn window!
媽的
Shit!
你留在這裏 不要動
You stay here and don't you move,
你聽到了嗎
you hear me?
我們得撤退
We gotta move!
操
Fuck...
這就對了滾回去
Oh yeah, take your asses home.
放開我 放開我
Let me go! Let me go!
這不值得 孩子 她會殺了你的
Not worth it, kid, she'll kill you.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我在乎
I do.
赫利俄斯擋住了它們
Helios held them back,
但我們還是犧牲了六個
but we still lost six.
嘿 看看我們抓到誰了
Hey, look who we found.
把他放地下室去
Put him in the basement!
別擔心 我們要慢慢地壓榨他
Don't worry, we're gonna squeeze him,
你是對的 我們早該殺了那個聖滾者
You were right. We should of killed that Holy Roller
阿門
Amen.
外面還有多少你這種上帝的敗類
How many Jesus junkies are out there?
非常多
There's plenty more.
多得你數不過來
More than you could count.
你們在哪兒宿營
Where ya campin'?
你們沒時間了
You're out of time...
問這有什麼用
what does it matter?
聽著 尤達
Well, Juda,
你不快速配合就得慢慢受折磨
we can do this fast, or we can do this slow.
這完全取決於你
It's totally up to you.
你們每個都會死
Every one of you is gonna die...
你們贏不了的
and you cant win,
因為上帝站在我們這一邊
not while we got God on our side.
你也知道
You know,
小神經最疼了
It's it's the small nerves that hurt the most.
知道我在說什麼嗎
You know what I'm saying?
你知道自己的
And do you realize just how many small nerves
指尖有多少的小神經嗎
you got in your finger tips?
相當多
You got lots.
是上帝派它們來的
God has sent them.
上帝是偉大的
God is great.
上帝在我體內
God is in me.
而她是他的劍
And She is his sword.
現在 現在 現在 現在
Now, now, now, now...
那個長尖牙的是誰
Who is this fang twat
她找我們幹嘛
and what does she want with us anyway?
她是來找我的
She's after me.
我昨天晚上猶豫著沒說
I wasn't sure 'till last night.
她是種新型吸血鬼
She's something new.
會繁殖後代的
A breeder.
不久前前我殺了她孩子
I killed her squirt a while back,
刺瞎了她一隻眼睛
I took her eye out...
她利用你來找到我
She used you to find me.
對不起 孩子
I'm sorry, kid.
這不值得 對嗎
That ain't worth shit, is it?
讓你回憶起某人了嗎
Remind you of someone?
你最好在它們來之前
You better get your people up the mountain
把你的人都轉移到山上
before they get here.
一號急令 一號急令
Code one. Code one.
所有人員都將在19時撤走
All personnel will evacuate at 19:00 hours.
只把必要的物品打包帶上
Pack only what is necessary.
到院子裏集合等候進一步的指示
Meet in the courtyard for further instructions.
這是一次疏散
This is evac...
你有計劃嗎
You got a plan?
有
YUP
等到那個婊子現身
I'm gonna wait till that bitch shows up
然後給她一刀
and I'm gonna take it to her.
送死可不是個好計劃孩子
Dying ain't much of a plan, boy.
我真的不在乎
I really don't give a shit.
死就死
Dead's dead,
帶上她陪葬
as long as I take her with me.
她想要我以眼還眼
She wants to hurt me like I hurt her.
是的 你會離開這兒的
Yep, and you're leavin'.
是啊 也許沒法離開
Yeah, maybe not.
如果我留下來
If I stay,
殺不了她的話 那咱們就得死
we stake her ass or we die trying.
不管怎樣
Either way,
咱們等這些人上山再說
we buy these folks some time to make it up the mountain.
好
Okay-
Okay.
你和我
You and me.
不 不 不 你們兩個刑柱之主
No, no, no, no, you Stakelanders
以為單憑兩個人就能殺了她
think you're gonna do this on your own?
獨享所有樂趣嗎
Just the two of you?
你們又會到大麻煩的
Have all the fun? You got another thing coming.
是的
Yeah,
墨西哥起我們就一直逃跑
we been running ever since Mexico.
個人來說 我有點累了
Personally, I'm a little tired of it.
這不是你的戰鬥 醫生
This ain't your fight, Doc.
我們四個人都可能死掉
Odds are all four of us are gonna die.
是的 我聽說過 不管怎樣結局都是死
Yeah well, I hear that's gonna happen anyway.
所以為什麼我們不積極面對了
So why don't we make it count.
振作起來
Cheer up!
放鬆 放鬆
Easy, Easy
好的 對不起
Okay, I'm sorry.
都準備好了可以走了
We got it all wired up, it's good to go.
那些吸血鬼 不知道自己會被什麼擊中
Fuckin' blood bags won't know what hit 'em.
誰在戰鬥結束後存活下來
Now, if anybody is left when it's over,
就往山上去
head for the mountains.
好的
Yeah.
讓我們殺死那些該死的吸血鬼 嗯
Let's kill some goddamn blood suckers, eh?
小心身後
Watch your back.
只把必要的物品打包帶上
到院子裏集合等候進一步的指示
這是一次疏散
一號急令
我重複一遍這是一次疏散
她會有事嗎
She's gonna be alright.
我女兒的名字叫 羅斯
My daughter's name was Rose.
你這樣還能瞄的准嗎
Are you sure you're gonna be able to shoot straight?
不喝才瞄不準
Couldn't shoot straight without it.
搞什麼鬼
What the hell?
他們從後面來了
Comin' from the back!
噢 天啊 它在從這兒經
Oh, jeez!  There's movement here
快快 快移動
Come on. Come on. Come on, move it!
你留在這兒 看著車子
Stay here. Watch the camp.
好
Qkay...
她要對我們使詐
She's trying to pull a fast one on us.
是的 沒錯
Yeah, well,
它們可以採取任何方式
they can come and get it any way they want.
咱們等他們靠近再說
Let's wait 'till they're close,
我們不想浪費彈藥
we don't wanna waste ammo.
他們在做什麼
What the hell are they doing?
他們為什麼停下
Why are they stopping?
管它為什麼
I don't need this shit.
咱們開火吧
Let's light 'em up!
這跑來個人
We got a runner!
就在前面 嘿
Up front! Hey!
他正朝著發電機方向跑去
He's heading for the genny!
嘿
Hey!
快離開那個
Get your asses--
媽的
Well, shit!
到前面去 到前面去
Back up front, back up front!
嘿
Hey!
快 快 進去 把它們往這邊引
Come on, Bat. Lead 'em this way.
來呀 你個婊子
Come on, you bitch!
你想抓我 過來試試
You want me? Come and get some!
繼續跑 這條路
Keep going! This way!
你沒打中她心臟他媽的
You missed the heart, goddammit!
媽的
Shit!
該死的
Damn!
我們被壓制住了
We're pinned down, man.
如果我們出去
We're not getting out.
我們不能出去
We're not getting out of this one!
不 我們不能
No, we ain't.
你得這麼做
You gotta do it!
我得這麼做
We gotta do it.
你必須這樣做
You got to do it!
我在這裏 婊子
I'm over here, bitch!
結果她 孩子
Finish her, kid.
感覺好點了嗎
You feel better?
沒有
No...
只是沒覺得更糟
but I don't feel worse.
我現在感覺跟狗屎一樣
I feel like shit.
你看上去跟狗屎一樣
You look like shit.
這是一次偉大的旅程 巴特
It's been a great ride, Bat.
這是一次偉大的旅程
It's been a great ride.
我愛你
I love you.
現在讓我們送這些吸血鬼下地獄去吧
Now, let's take these bloodsuckers to Hell.
走 老頭 我們走吧
Come on, old man.
她死了
She's gone.
沒有
No
女士
' Lady?
是我 他是先生
It's me... It's Mister.
你認識我的
You know me.
放鬆 女孩
Easy, girl.
不 女孩
No, girl.
不 不 不
No,no,no,no.
別這樣
No please
先生
Mister...
我沒法再堅持了 孩子
I can't do this anymore, kid.
千萬不要這麼想
Don't even think about it.
我會盡可能久的給你拖住它們
I'll buy you as much time as I can.
不
No.
不 我要留下咱們一起戰鬥
No, I'm gonna stay and we'll fight.
一個男人總是希望 他的兒子比他更出色
A man wants his son to be better than he is.
記住
Git.
我不知道後來他怎麼樣了
I don't know what happened to him.
我想這不重要
Guess it doesn't matter.
但我知道我會再見到他
But I know I'll see him again.
不是在這個地獄就是在下一個地獄
In this Hell or the next.